Class of 1880 Records, 1877-1949
Smith College Archives
Class of 1880 Records
1877-1949
Smith College. Class of 1880.
RG 80
1 box (5 linear inches)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains black and white photographs, letters, correspondence, programs, invitations, songs, and other information about the graduation and reunions of the Class of 1880.
Historical Note
The Class of 1880 was the second graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1880 Records contain materials describing the history of the students of the Class of 1880. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, correspondence, programs, invitations, songs, and other information about the graduation and reunions of the Class of 1880.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1880 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class of 1880: Commencement 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 1)
- Class of 1880: Commencement Speaker 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 2)
- Class of 1880: Commencement Music 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 3)
- Class of 1880: Songs 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 4)
- Class of 1880: Group Photographs 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 5)
- Class of 1880: Poetry 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 6)
- Class of 1880: Reunions N.d. (Box 1380, Folder 7)
- Class of 1880: Reunions 1905 (Box 1380, Folder 8)
- Class of 1880: Reunions 1910 (Box 1380, Folder 9)
- Class of 1880: Reunions 1925 (Box 1380, Folder 10)
- Class of 1880: Reunions 1930 (Box 1380, Folder 11)
- Class of 1880: Reunions 1935 (Box 1380, Folder 12)
- Class of 1880: Reunions 1940 (Box 1380, Folder 13)
- Class of 1880: Bisbee, Anna Bartlett 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 14)
- Class of 1880: Bisbee, Mary Otis 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 15)
- Class of 1880: Clark, Josephine Adelaide (Box 1380, Folder 16)
- Class of 1880: Devoll, Ida Eugenia 1880, 1930-34, 1936 (Box 1380, Folder 17)
- Class of 1880: Eaton, Ella Elizabeth (Box 1380, Folder 18)
- Class of 1880: Gorham, Anna Kellogg 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 19)
- Class of 1880: Locke, Mary Stoughton 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 20)
- Class of 1880: Locke, Mary Stoughton (Correspondence) 1900, 1930-34, 1936-38, 1940, 1945, 1949 (Box 1380, Folder 21)
- Class of 1880: Miller, Helen Lyman (Correspondence: Sept.-Nov.) 1877 (Box 1380, Folder 22)
- Class of 1880: Miller, Helen Lyman (Correspondence: Dec.-Feb.) 1877-1878 (Box 1380, Folder 23)
- Class of 1880: Miller, Helen Lyman (Correspondence: Mar.-Apr.) 1878 (Box 1380, Folder 24)
- Class of 1880: Miller, Helen Lyman (Correspondence: May-June) 1878 (Box 1380, Folder 25)
- Class of 1880: Miller, Helen Lyman (Photographs) 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 26)
- Class of 1880: Robinson, Jennie Justina 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 27)
- Class of 1880: Seymour, May 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 28)
- Class of 1880: Tate, Emma (Correspondence) 1930-34, 1936-38, 1941 (Box 1380, Folder 29)
- Class of 1880: Tate, Emma (Photographs) 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 30)
- Class of 1880: Tuckerman, Lillian Ellinwood 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 31)
- Class of 1880: Toxbury, Helen (Correspondence) 1900, 1906, 1930-34, 1936-37 (Box 1380, Folder 32)
- Class of 1880: Toxbury, Helen (Photographs) 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 33)
- Class of 1880: Wetherbee, Netta Elizabeth (Correspondence) 1881, 1884-85, 1887, 1889-1910, 1912, 1914-16, 1918-25, 1927-32, 1934, 1936-38, 1940 (Box 1380, Folder 34)
- Class of 1880: Wetherbee, Netta Elizabeth (Photographs) 1880 (Box 1380, Folder 35)